soulmate2date.com 2007-10-18

# Subscribe now Free! look for new love with UK online dating

## Privacy Policy

This Web site is operated by Soulmate2date.com.

All data is owned and managed by Soulmate2date.com

### Soulmate2date.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.

### The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

Data Protection Act 1998:  Soulmate2date.com is registered with the Data Protection Registrar No. Z9934213 and confirms that all personal data handled and stored by us is done so in strict compliance with the latest Data Protection Act 1998. 

Information Automatically Logged:  We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site, and to help identify you and your chosen set up of the web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, and for other purposes. 

Cookies:  Our Site uses cookies to keep track of your chosen set up of the web site, and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes. 

Registration Forms:  Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like your name, and email address), and demographic information (like your post/zipcode, age, or interests). Contact information from the registration forms is used to help us find you your (Ideal Partner). The customer's contact information is also used to send promotional material from some of our partners to our customers, and to get in touch with the customer when necessary. 

Surveys:  Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like your name, and email address), and demographic information (like your post/zipcode, age, or interests). Contact information from the surveys is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary, and for other purposes.

Contests:  We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like your name, and email address), and demographic information (like your post/zipcode, age, or interests). 

External Links:  This site contains links to other sites. Soulmate2date.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites. 

Public Forums:  This site makes your profile available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

Choice/Opt-Out:  Our site provides users the opportunity to delete their profile at any time by selecting the (Cancel My Membership) option in the Membership Summary section.

Data Quality/Access:  Users can change any information provided by using the (Edit My Profile) feature.

Contacting the Web Site:  If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please do not hesitate to contact us.
